So the only generator I could find.
I have tried to get mine started, but no, it is not possible.
It is a bit special with because it sits only a coil in this
so they must have a special charge regulator
and it is a regulator that is constantly lying
And pulses power into the winding.
So a modern charge regulator does not work.
So I bought a charge regulator, an electronic,
And bought new winding.
But no, I didn't get that started.
Don't charge anything.
And there is to buy.
One has found Europe down in Belgium and then guy there.
One?
One, he had.
But he knew it was unusual.
12,000 plus tax plus shipping and a little.
Yes.
No, it's not that fun.
I mean damn it is more than what half the bike is worth
so to speak.
So I went a bit and looked in the hides here in the garage
And then I found an alternator generator.
And it starts to giggle like this.
So you have to fix that.
I have ripped a whole electrical system, all the cables and this.
It's not good MC cables because they are.
If you look at these, there are very few threads so such a cable
becomes very stiff.
The stiffer the cable you have the easier it goes by vibration.
This is how you want a cable that has a lot of threads
which becomes soft and compliant.
Then he can lie down and vibrate without such a thing.
The engine vibrates very much so then it is important